

ELLIOT PARKER

SKILLS

- DAX, PowerQuery (4 yrs)
- Python, R (4 yrs)
- SQL, NoSQL, Postgres (4 yrs)
- Microsoft Power BI (5 yrs)
- SSIS, SSAS (4 yrs)
- Machine Learning Regression
 & Classification (4 yrs)
- Azure, AWS, GC (4 yrs)
- Tableau, Google DataStudio, Zoho Analytics (2 yrs)
- Salesforce, Zoho CRM (4 yrs)
- Google Adwords, Facebook Ads (4 yrs)
- Zendesk, Freshdesk (5 yrs)
- Square, Xero (4 yrs)
- Supermetrics, Funnel (2yrs)
- MailChimp, Campaign Monitor (4 yrs)

CONTACT

ELLIOTP18@GMAIL.COM

M: +507 601 780 72

PROFILE

A Business Intelligence Specialist with over four years' experience in the design, development, and deployment of a broad variety of analytics solutions. A versatile team member and leader with experience handling sensitive business & personal information as well as assisting in key strategic decision making.

Experience in full time & consultant positions across a range of company sizes and industries including technology, finance, marketing, and hospitality.

Extremely creative with a genuine belief in the power of visualization and the immense opportunities created by analytics. Comfortable with a wide variety of coding languages, software platforms, tools, and packages.

EXPERIENCE

DATA BACKEND ENGINEER (REMOTE)

DATAWALLET | MAR 2019 - SEP 2019

An early stage funded technology start-up which allows for everyone to be able to govern, permission and the audit the use of all of their data. Notable investors include Salesforce's CEO Marc Benioff and Tim Draper. Based in Berlin, Germany.

Advised, designed, developed and deployed a new Solutions Architecture to support the company's rapid growth and new level of maturity. Developed a large number of dashboards, reports, and insights across a variety of business areas including User Behavior, Marketing and Support.

Key challenges included strict governance requirements, the sensitivity of the underlying data and the exponentially expanding series of datasets. Primary responsibilities also included liaising with the board, employees & other stakeholders with respect to the insights and questions they would like answered.

SNR BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE SPECIALIST

UNGER CONSULTING | JAN 2018 - SEP 2019

A boutique consulting firm specializing in the business development, finance and marketing of early stage ventures. Clients have included Vodafone, Ducati and a number of Softbank, Tencent & Salesforce funded companies.

Based in Melbourne, Australia.

Designed, developed and deployed a multitude of dashboards & complex solutions architectures for fast growing start-ups across a range of industries.

Created insights across Product, Sales, Marketing and Support as well as have worked with a large number of tools and unique data sources. Broad experience working with and creating Data Warehouses, API Integrations and complex resilient ETL pipelines.

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE ANALYST

NEOSCONA ANALYTICS | APR 2015 - JAN 2018

A hospitality business intelligence SaaS start up founded as a result of the intellectual property created & developed with The Poppy & Maude Group. Based in Canberra, Australia.

Designed, developed and deployed complex SSAS Tabular Cubes, Microsoft Power BI Data-models as well as the Solution's Architecture.

Personally created a large number of proprietary insights relating to Sales Forecasting, Product Management, Stock Management, and Employee Timetabling. Directly responsible for the Machine Learning Regression & Classification modelling as well as the live deployment.

Liaised with key technical & service partners as well as helped to create, support and on board every single early client.

CERTIFCATIONS

Microsoft Power BI Solution Partner

Microsoft Silver Partner

Microsoft Power BI Accelerator

REFERENCES

Maximilian Unger
Founder, Chief Executive Officer
DATAWALLET
UNGER CONSULTING

Mirko Immerso
Chief Executive Officer
NEOSCONA ANALYTICS

Claudi Algeshi Group Operating Officer THE POPPY & MAUDE GROUP

Contact information available upon request

INVESTMENT ANALYST

FOLKESTONE REAL ESTATE INVESTMENT TRUST | JAN 2016 - DEC 2017

An ASX listed REIT recently acquired by the Charter Hall group. The dual focuses of the trust was funds management & commercial property development.

Based in Sydney, Australia.

Responsible for financial and data modelling efforts contributing to a successful development proposal to build a premium retirement village on Sydney's North Shore.

Actively contributed to the research, financial and portfolio modelling relating to the REIT's benchmark and peer out-performance.

Duties also included communicating with federal and state government regulatory bodies in conjunction with key partners and shareholders.

EVENT & OPERATIONS MANAGER

THE POPPY & MAUDE GROUP | JAN 2015 - JAN 2018

An independently owned hospitality group including two large (250+ seat) Cafes as well as a high volume Takeaway Cafe.
Based in Canberra, Australia.

Directly responsible for the creation of numerous products, events and promotions across all three venues. Negotiated, organized and managed multiple large (600+) government, corporate and private events. Frequent liaisons with sensitive and influential stakeholders including the Prime Minister's Office, PwC, E&Y as well as the group's ownership.

Responsible for the management of a team (~65) across a range of roles and functions including multiple tender proposals and contract bidding. Duties also included timetabling staff, managing stock and contributing to wider group strategy.

Crucial in the foundation of Neoscona Analytics and the meaningful use of company developed business intelligence insights. Fundamentally reshaped and created new workflows, processes and manners of engagement which as a result affected our approach to customers.

PORTFOLIO

Neoscona Analytics

We created three SaaS products each focused upon specific goals, time horizons and user groups. The designs were created as Microsoft Power BI was released and thus lack the modern aesthetic polish.

Summer: https://imgur.com/a/kBNIK Rhythm: https://imgur.com/a/vcfzS Melody: https://imgur.com/a/aOrgu

 * A large amount of my portfolio has been created under strict NDAs.

EDUCATION

The Australian National University 2012-2016

Bachelor of Commerce & Economics Majors in Economics and Finance

Geelong Grammar School 2008-2011

International Baccalaureate

Higher Level Subjects: Economics, Chemistry, German